lacounty.gov 2014-06-02

# Los Angeles County-About This Site-Privacy Policy

The Board of Supervisors of Los Angeles County recognizes the public's concern about privacy on the Internet. This privacy statement establishes how information gathered about you from your visit to our website will be used by this website's operators. As a visitor, however, you should be aware that much information submitted to Los Angeles County is public information under the laws of the State of California. Under some circumstances, we may be required to disclose such information in accordance with the California Public Records Act or other legal requirements.

The following describes how information may be collected depending on your activities at this website:

 **If you read or download information:** We may collect and store information for statistical purposes. For example, we may count the number of visitors to the different sections of our site to help us make them more useful. The information collected may include such items as the name and domain of the host from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using or your browser software and operating system. This information does not identify you personally.

 **If you send E-mail to this website:** By sending us an electronic mail message, you may be sending us personal information (i.e., your name, address, e-mail address, etc.). We may store the name and address of the requester in order to respond to the request or otherwise resolve the subject matter of your e-mail.

 **If you register with a County Department or agency or request other specific information:**

Some County department or agency websites may ask visitors who request specific information to fill out a registration form. For example, vendors requesting access to Requests for Bids, Requests for Proposals or homeowners or businesses requesting Permits, may be asked to provide their names, addresses, e-mail addresses and other pertinent information to ensure we can process and deliver the information requested. Other information may be collected at these sites through questionnaires, feedback forms, or other means, to enable us to determine a visitor's interests, with the goal of providing better service.

 **Privacy Statements for Other County Departmental or Agency Websites** This privacy statement describes the information gathering practices and procedures of the County of Los Angeles Home Page, however, the domain is made up of many departmental and agency websites linked together to provide a comprehensive information resource to our residents. Accordingly, each department or agency website within the domain of the County of Los Angeles has posted specific information concerning its information gathering practices. You may review the privacy statement for each website within this domain by selecting the "Privacy" icon on the navigation bar of each page.

 **Links to Non-Los Angeles County (Third Party) Websites**

Our website also contains links to information located on websites maintained by other public agencies and private organizations. Once you access an individual document that links you to another website, you are subject to the privacy policy of the website containing that document.

 **Disclaimer of Liability** With respect to information available from this web page, neither the County of Los Angeles nor any of its employees, make any warranty, express or implied, including the warranty of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose, or assume any liability or responsibility for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of such information.
